ILGWU. Wilbur Daniels papers, 5780/084
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III. General/Administrative, 1937-1985
  - Legislation. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Undated. Memo re Javits' bill on labor relations; re H.R. 15402; correspondence re Committee Hearing to Discuss Attorney General's Pension Bill November 5, 1971; re Rural Development Act of 1972; memo re Labor Law Reform Bill; re Discrimination Against Prior Alcoholics; with Hon. Ken Holland, US House of Representatives; correspondence re Hollings Amendment to S. 3077; re CETA language; Pregnancy Amendment to Title VII; routine
  - Legislation. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Liberal Party, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Correspondence re Joseph Pomarlen, member of Liberal Party
  - Local Unions, 1966-1978 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Correspondence re Anna Guelfi, Local 129 - Ledger 7367; Local 1964; Local 20; President's Report - Local 30 Trusteeship; Local 189; Local 275; Puerto Rico District Council; routine
  - McClellan Committee. Kenrose Material. [folder 1 of 2], 1945-1954 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Agreement with Puritan Mills, Inc.; Agreement with Benrose Manufacturing Company 1945; newspaper clippings; Report of Engineering Department of Benrose Manufacturing Company(later Benrose); Agreement with Kenrose Manufacturing Company; Report on Kenrose Manufacturing Co. by Management of Engineering Dept.
  - McClellan Committee. Kenrose Material. [folder 2 of 2], 1945-1954 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Minimum Wage. Federal, 1970-1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Hearings Transcripts: Committee on Labor and Public Welfare - Fair Labor Standards Amendments of 1971; correspondence with Commonwealth of Puerto Rico; Statement of Andrew J. Biemiller, Director Department of Legislation AFL-CIO, before the Labor and Public Welfare Committee on S. 1861, Legislation to Amend the Fair Labor Standards Act; Statement of Jacob Potofsky; Amendments to Fair Labor Standards Act - statement presented by ILGWU
  - New School for Social Research, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Correspondence of Haldi Associates, Inc. - Economic and Management Counsel; "Drug use, the labor market, and class conflict" by John Helmer and Thomas Victorisz; Resumes of Haldi Associates; Narrative by Haldi Associates
  - New York State Constitutional Conventional. [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    "Issues for the 1967 Constitutional Convention" by Professor Jack B. Weinstein; Outline of Remarks by David Wells at meeting of Democratic Candidates for New York State Constitution Convention - "How can the State Constitution be revised to provide a fair, workable system of apportionment and districting?"; correspondence re Temporary State Commission on Constitution; Statement of Louis Stulberg to Temporary State Commission; AFL-CIO Executive Council Statement on Proposals for Federal Legislation To Regulate Health and Welfare and Pension Plans; Present Constitutional Provisions Relating to Labor, Civil Service, and Public Pensions; memo re New York State AFL-CIO "Labor Bill of Rights"; re AFL-CIO statement on Benefits Funds Legislation; Statement by William L. Lincoln, American Life Convention and Life Insurance Association of America, before Committee on Labor, Civil Service, and Public Pensions; Statement of Commerce and Industry Association of New York, Inc.; correspondence with Liberal Party Delegation; Interim Report Committee on Labor, Civil Service, and Public Pensions; routine
  - New York State Constitutional Conventional. [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - New York State AFL-CIO. [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    State Legislative Program, Liberal Party - "Public Health"; Statement on Proposed Administration Health Insurance Plan; correspondence re New York State Constitution; Proposed Changes in Proposition 100; correspondence with Raymond Corbett, President of New York AFL-CIO; Congressional Record - "Campaign Underway To Rewrite National Labor Relations Act"; Memorandum S. 9181 - Rules "Universal Health Insurance Program"; memo re State AFL-CIO resolutions; routine
  - New York State AFL-CIO. [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1973 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Personnel. [folder 1 of 2], 1974-1981 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Memo re Data for Personnel Review Committee meeting; Personnel Review Committee; resumes and references; routine
  - Personnel. [folder 2 of 2], 1974-1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Pins and Needles. [folder 1 of 4], 1976-1987 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Mostly 1978. Newspaper clippings; Notes; Reviews; correspondence with Roundabout Theatre Company; Address Lists; Invitation Lists; "Pins and Needles" Programs; routine
  - Pins and Needles. [folder 2 of 4], 1976-1987 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Pins and Needles. [folder 3 of 4], 1976-1987 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Pins and Needles. [folder 4 of 4], 1976-1987 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Political. [folder 1 of 3], 1968-1979 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Location of ILGWU Locals by States and Congressional Districts; correspondence with Fredrick Warder, Chairman Assembly Committee on Labor; Requests from Candidates Seeking House Seats; Mexican-American Garment Industries Committee - Minutes; "Why Exports Are Becoming Irrelevant" by Lawrence B. Krause; newspaper clippings; Speech by Senator Ed Kennedy; correspondence with Hubert Humphrey; Remarks of Raymond Corbett, President of AFL-CIO; memo on Contributions to State and Local Candidates in View of Tax Problems; Labor Committee for Carey; memo re Regulation of Lobbying in New York; "The Case Against Nelson Rockefeller" by Jack Newfield; routine
  - Political. [folder 2 of 3], 1968-1979 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Political. [folder 3 of 3], 1968-1979 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Research Department, 1961-1967 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    List of Firms Manufacturing Women's and Children's Garments With a Capitalization of Over $1,000,000; Companies Involved In Recent Mergers Or Acquisitions (1961); List of Publicly-Owned Firms Manufacturing Women's and Children's Garments (1962); Sales, Net Profits, and Net Worth, Women's Garment Industry (1964); Survey of 13 Large Garment Companies; Proposed Policy With Regard to Learner's Under ILGWU Agreements; "Earnings in Women's and Children's and Misses' Coat and Suit Industry"; Decision - Case No. 26993 v. American Couture; "conditions in the Women's Garment Industry" - Research Department; Philadelphia and Reading Corporation; routine
  - Research Department, 1967-1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Report on Work of ILGWU Research Department; Learner Regulations in Apparel Industries; Learner Exemptions Granted by Wage and Hour Division; correspondence with Dr. Lazar Teper; Digest of New York Unemployment Insurance Law; Garment Imports - Resolution; "Conditions in the Women's Garment Industry - 1969"; New Rules On Retroactivity; routine
  - Research Department, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Key Provisions of Wage Regulations; "Conditions in Women's Garment Industry - 1972"; memo from John Gates re Federal Standard for Appeals Promptness - Unemployment Compensation; correspondence with Governor Nelson Rockefeller re Benefits; routine
  - Resumes. [folder 1 of 6], 1974-1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Resumes; correspondence re resumes, recommendations, references; routine
  - Resumes. [folder 2 of 6], 1974-1985 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Resumes. [folder 3 of 6], 1974-1985 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Resumes. [folder 4 of 6], 1974-1985 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Resumes. [folder 5 of 6], 1974-1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Resumes. [folder 6 of 6], 1974-1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Retirement Fund. ILGWU Staff. [folder 1 of 3], 1958-1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    ILGWU Staff Retirement Fund Summary and Plan; Actuarial Valuation and Cost Study of Proposed Amendments 12/31/70; AFL-CIO Staff Retirement Plan; correspondence re ILGWU Staff Retirement Plan; Staff Retirement Fund Changes; Problems and Questions - Staff Retirement Fund; Revised Summary of New Plan; Requests For Retroactive Participation; memo re request for exception from mandatory retirement; ILGWU National Fund - Meeting of Board of Trustees; routine
  - Retirement Fund. ILGWU Staff. [folder 2 of 3], 1958-1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Retirement Fund. ILGWU Staff. [folder 3 of 3], 1958-1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Schifter, Margaret Hoyt, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Correspondence re Catalyst - non-profit organization for women college graduates to find employment
  - Social Security Legislation. City Bar Association Committee on Labor and Security Legislation, 1965- 1966 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Committee Member List; correspondence re committee; Proposed Bill to Amend Sections of National Labor Relations Act (S. 2395); "Procedural Reform - First Step Toward A More Effective National Labor Policy" by Hon. John H. Fanning; Proposed Amendments to National Emergency Provisions of Taft-Hartley Act; Proposed State Legislation Concerning Public Employee Disputes; memo of Committee on State Legislation; Proposed Amendments to Federal Equal Employment Opportunity Legislation; Report on Proposed Limitations of Label Suits in Connection with Labor Disputes; Proposed State Legislation Concerning Public Employee Relations; Draft Report of Sub-Committee on Fair Representation; Meeting Minutes; routine
  - Special Committee On Low Wage Workers, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Board of Directors List; "Some Facts Relating To Earnings and Wages in New York City"
  - Spitz, Milton. Assistant General Auditor (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Correspondence re Firms Under Master Agreement; Multi-Plant Firms; Investment Policy; Special Assistance Fund - collections for non-union contractors; correspondence re status of audit bills; Grace Period; Local Autonomy; memo re Majestic Specialties Welfare Funds Control Department; Master Contract Fringe Benefit Rates; routine
  - Stock Market Clippings, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Stulberg, Louis. Brandeis Dinner. [folder 1 of 4], 1968-1972 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Correspondence re Brandeis University Dinner for Induction of Louis Stulberg as a Fellow; reservations; guest lists; invitations; committee lists; speech; routine
  - Stulberg, Louis. Brandeis Dinner. [folder 2 of 4], 1968-1972 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Stulberg, Louis. Brandeis Dinner. [folder 3 of 4], 1968-1972 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Stulberg, Louis. Brandeis Dinner. [folder 4 of 4], 1968-1972 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Stulberg, Louis. Correspondence with Wilbur Daniels. [folder 1 of 3], 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    Correspondence re proposed legislation requiring vesting and funding; 25% damages for non-union contractors; newspaper clippings; correspondence re pension fund legislation; General Office - Schedule of Organization and Strike Fund; correspondence re ILGWU Constitution; ILGWU 1968 Census Report; Average Hourly Earnings, Dress Industry; correspondence re corset and brassiere out-of-town agreement; Student Loan Program; Dress Industry Hourly Earnings; No-strike clause; proposed legislation on welfare and pension plans; Agreement with Rosenau Brothers, Inc.; correspondence re supplemental benefits for retired officers; group insurance; salary increases for union officials; Federal Trade Commission Advisory Opinion on Imports; routine
  - Stulberg, Louis. Correspondence with Wilbur Daniels. [folder 2 of 3], 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Stulberg, Louis. Correspondence with Wilbur Daniels. [folder 3 of 3], 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Stulberg, Louis. Correspondence with Wilbur Daniels. [folder 1 of 3] (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Correspondence re 1969 Census Report; AFL-CIO Committee on Minimum Wage; Financial and Statistical Report 1968-70; ILGWU Staff Retirement Fund; ILGWU Welfare Funds Collection Account; ILGWU in Canada; Imports; "Coalition For A Rural America"; Hartke - Burke: bill on imports; notes; routine
  - Stulberg, Louis. Correspondence with Wilbur Daniels. [folder 2 of 3] (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Stulberg, Louis. Correspondence with Wilber Daniels. [folder 3 of 3] (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Supplementary Unemployment. Severance Benefits Fund, 1960-1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Rules and Regulations; correspondence re contract provision on union-made products; Court of Special Sessions re Section 962-a of Penal Law; correspondence re Supplementary Unemployment Benefits Plan; routine
  - Tri-State Airport Authority, 1965-1968 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Correspondence re Tri-State Airport Authority with Attorney Charles Bagley; re improvement project; routine
  - Tri-State Airport Authority Bonds. [folder 1 of 6], 1951-1963 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Investment Analysis Department re Tri-State Airport Authority Revenue Bonds; Housing Authority of Luzerne County, Pennsylvania; Chapter 142, Bill No. 48: Tri-State Airport Authority Authorized; Meisel v. Tri-State Airport Authority; Tri-State Airport Authority Bond Records; Air Transport and Tri-State Airport Authority Hearing; notes; Record of Audit; Concession Contracts Listing; correspondence with Chemical Bank of New York Trust Company re bonds; Real Estate and Improvements; amendments to the Federal Airport Act, 1961; Review of Investments; correspondence re Bonds of Housing Authority of Luzerne County and Tri-State Airport Authority; Sixteenth Annual Report of operations under Federal Airport Act, 1961; Resolution and Order re Tri-State Airport Authority; Financial Statements; correspondence with Attorney Charles Bagley; newspaper clippings; correspondence with Tri-State Airport Authority re default on bonds; National Airport Plan Requirements for Fiscal Years 1962-66; routine
  - Tri-State Airport Authority Bonds. [folder 2 of 6], 1951-1963 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Tri-State Airport Authority Bonds. [folder 3 of 6], 1951-1963 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Tri-State Airport Authority Bonds. [folder 4 of 6], 1951-1963 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Tri-State Airport Authority Bonds. [folder 5 of 6], 1951-1963 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Tri-State Airport Authority Bonds. [folder 6 of 6], 1951-1963 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Trussel Report, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Study of Population Characteristics and Hospitalization Experience 1965
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1963-1966 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    New York Unemployment Insurance Law - Vacation Period or Holiday; Alternative Approaches to Compensation of Partial Unemployment Under the New York State Unemployment Insurance Law; Study of Impact of a Loss of Earnings Plan for Payment of Partial Unemployment Under New York State Unemployment Insurance Law; Statement on behalf of ILGWU before New York State Joint Legislative Committee on Unemployment Insurance, presented by Walter Mankoff, Acting Assistant Director of Research; Proposed Act to amend labor law in relation to method of payment of benefits for partial unemployment under unemployment insurance law; correspondence with New York State Department of Labor Division of Employment; Explanatory Statement: Benefits for Partial Employment - Replacement of Day Base Plan; routine
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1966-1971 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Correspondence with Alfred Green, New York State Department of Labor Division of Unemployment; correspondence re Partial Unemployment; Changes between 1966 and 1967 proposed amendments to Unemployment Insurance Law; Local 62 Holiday Pay; correspondence re New York State Unemployment Insurance Law Changes; Unemployment Benefit Advisors - Senate Hearings on Unemployment Compensation Bill; Unemployment Insurance Reports "Mississippi Enacts Conforming Amendments"; routine
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1971-1979 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Proposed Act to amend labor law in relation to taxable wages and rates of contributions under Unemployment Insurance Law; Unemployment Insurance Reports; State of Connecticut - Memorandum on behalf of ILGWU Opposing Disqualifications from Unemployment Insurance Benefits; ILGWU Statement: Maximum Weekly Benefit Rate Under New York Unemployment Insurance Law; memo re Cutoff of Extended and Emergency Unemployment Compensation Programs in New York State; Significant Provisions of State Unemployment Insurance Laws; routine
  - Union Health Center. Financial Reports. [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1972 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Union Health Center. Financial Reports. [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1972 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Union Health Center. Dr. Conrad Rosenberg. [folder 1 of 3], 1967-1985 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Report of Union Health Center and Hospital Benefit Program - Maz Shain; correspondence re Union Health Center; Report for Union Health Center Committee of G.E.B.; "Review of Medical Services" by Dr. Conrad Rosenberg; memo from Sol Berger, Administrative Director, re Comments on Dr. Conrad Rosenberg's survey; Annual Report of Medical Director - Dr. Herbert Newman; Minutes of Meeting of Union Health Center Committee of G.E.B., ILGWU; routine
  - Union Health Center. Dr. Conrad Rosenberg. [folder 2 of 3], 1967-1985 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Union Health Center. Dr. Conrad Rosenberg. [folder 3 of 3], 1967-1985 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Union Label, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Newspaper clippings; correspondence re TV commercials; union label advertisements; Notes on ILGWU; Union Label Song; routine
  - Venice Industries, Inc., 1971 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    Correspondence re Venice Industries, Inc.; new plant set-up; routine
  - Wage Freeze, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    ILGWU Application For Decontrol of Wages in the Women's Garment Industry Before Cost of Living Council; Procedural Regulations Under Wage Price Controls cost of Living Council, Pay Board, and Internal Revenue Service; Simplified guide to Pay Board Regulations; correspondence re Pay Board; Executive Order - Providing For Stabilization of Prices, Rents, Wages, and Salaries; correspondence from Walter Mankoff re Applicability of wage freeze to increase dues under agreement with Apparel Manufacturers' Association of PR, Inc.; routine
  - Welfare Funds Collection Account. [folder 1 of 3], 1960-1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Correspondence re Welfare Funds Collection Account; Out-of-town welfare funds auditing procedures; Monthly Report on welfare funds by Boston Joint Board; Special Assistance Fund Statement - non-union contractor's list; correspondence re Recommendations for report to G.E.B.; Handmacher-Vogel, Inc. and subsidiaries, Tailored Trends, Couture Specialties, Country Miss, Country, Jr.; Henry Rosenfeld; memo from Welfare Funds Control Department; Collection of welfare funds and liquidated damages; Welfare Funds Collection Account - Audits; Credit Report on Vanity Fair Mills; correspondence re survey of procedures; correspondence re Inter-affiliate Health and Welfare Transfers of Employer Contributions; Restructuring of ILGWU "Employer Audit Program"; Delinquent Employer Contributions - 1975; routine
  - Welfare Funds Collection Account. [folder 2 of 3], 1960-1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Welfare Funds Collection Account. [folder 3 of 3], 1960-1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Welfare Fund Report. [folder 1 of 3 ], 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Correspondence re Welfare Fund of Fashion Accessories Industry; Funds Collection - Philadelphia Dress Joint Board; 1969 Report on Benefit Fund Charges and Collections; correspondence with Plastic, Moulders, and Novelty Workers' Union; with Dressmakers Union - Joint Council; correspondence re Vacation, Health, Death, and Welfare Fund; Amounts Due To Funds Which Were Waived Funds; correspondence with Welfare Funds Control Department; correspondence re Health, Education, and Welfare Advisory Committee on Automated Personal Data Systems; List of ILGWU Health and Welfare Funds; routine
  - Welfare Fund Report. [folder 2 of 3], 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Welfare Fund Report. [folder 3 of 3], 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Wolf and Schulman. Accountants, 1966-1970 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Correspondence with Wolf and Schulman; re suggested Examination of Books Clause; List of Members of Apparel Industries of New England presently operating through the Holiday Fund; routine
  - Miscellaneous A-E. [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    ACWA Retired Members Questionnaire; "Executive Prerequisites - impact of new disclosure and tax rules"; Analysis of a Union Campaign;American Arbitration Association - Executive Committee, Report to Annual Meeting; Miscellaneous and Routine
  - Miscellaneous A-E. [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1980 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous F-J. [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1978 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous F-J. [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1978 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous K-P. [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1979 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    MALDEF - Mexican American Legal Defense and Education Fund correspondence; Miscellaneous and Routine
  - Miscellaneous K-P. [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1979 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Q-S. [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1978 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Q-S. [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1978 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous T-Z. [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1984 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    Cassette tape of "Labor - Labor's View"; "Health Impact of Unemployment and Low Income"; Miscellaneous and Routine
  - Miscellaneous T-Z. [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1984 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous T-Z. [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1984 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1974-1979 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1974-1979 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - National Afro-American Labor Council, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People--Special Contribution Fund, 1967- 1972 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Emergency Voter Education Drives
  - National Association of Women's and Children's Apparel Salesmen, 1967-1969 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - National Board of Coat and Suit Industry, 1965-1967 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Statistics; reports; minutes of meetings
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing, 1967-1972 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Meetings; election nominations; financial difficulties; summary of court cases
  - New England Industries, Inc., 1966 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Analytical report
  - New England Sportswear Manufacturers Association, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Prohibition against Dealing with Amalgamated Shops
  - New York City Manpower Panel, 1965-1966 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    On-the-Job Training Programs
  - New York City Public Development Corporation [Folder 1 of 2], 1966-1972 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Public housing development; urban renewal areas; industrial districts; incorporation
  - New York City Public Development Corporation [Folder 2 of 2], 1966-1972 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - New York City (Box 33, Folder 11)
    Miscellaneous
  - New York Joint Cloak Board, 1964-1969 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Contract proposals
  - New York State Bar Association, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Member information; journal
  - Non-Assessables (Welfare Funds), 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    G.E.B. policy; financial information
  - O'Hare and Kroul, 1966-1970 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    Civil suit
  - Federal Advisory Council on Unemployment Insurance, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Federal Advisory Council on Unemployment Insurance, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    2 of 2
  - Federal Advisory Council on Unemployment Insurance Reports, 1973-1978 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - FAC on UI: Research Subcommittee, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    March 10
  - National Committee on Unemployment Compensation; memos, meeting materials, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    1 of 9
  - National Committee on Unemployment Compensation; memos, meeting materials, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    2 of 9
  - National Committee on Unemployment Compensation; memos, meeting materials, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    3 of 9
  - National Committee on Unemployment Compensation; memos, meeting materials, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    4 of 9
  - National Committee on Unemployment Compensation; memos, meeting materials, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    5 of 9